hi there
and Robert McEwan and this is a product
review for the chef's back HS 8200
millimeter table saw primarily the HSA
is the lighter duty compact animal soul
designed for the DIY enthusiast or for
lighter trade use as the AHSAA is quite
small in size and compact it is ideal
for anybody who was a limited amount of
workshop space but also because it only
weighs 15 kilos it's light and portable
and can be easily transported to where
the work is
some of the features which this saw has
is a powerful 1200 watt motor this
directly drives a 200 millimeter saw
blade which gives a 48 millimeter depth
of cut it also has a rigid RIP fence
which is lockable at both ends and has a
measuring scale at the front and one at
the rear to line the fence to be
parallel with the saw blade there is
also a sliding vanity guide included
which can be angle to 45 degrees both
ways
and there's also an extendable panel
support fence for supporting them wider
panels
the saw also comes with a duplex rise
fall and tilting system on the saw blade
this is not resin what was the body was
after releasing the locking knob the
blade can be angled forward to 45
degrees that is also at the rear adjust
extraction port for extracting away the
dust finally the HS 80 is both
economical to buy and can also cut a
wide range of timber section narrow
boards and small panels both accurately
and efficiently and will be an ideal
tool for any small workshop